Guide to the Men's Basketball Game Film Collection, 1947-1996 UA.13.01.0005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Men's Basketball Game Films
  - Wake Forest, 1972 December 16
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1972 December 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0875)
  - Harvard, 1972 December 30
    Duke win; score: 102-76
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 1, 1972 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0876)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 2, 1972 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0877)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 3, 1972 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0878)
    - Duke vs. Harvard: Reel 4, 1972 December 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 18, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0879)
  - Virginia, 1973 January 03
    Duke loss; score: 74-80
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1973 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0880)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1973 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0881)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1973 January 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0882)
  - Wake Forest, 1973 January 06
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0883)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0884)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0885)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0886)
  - Wake Forest, 1973 January 06
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0887)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0888)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0889)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1973 January 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0890)
  - NC State, 1973 January 10
    Duke loss; score: 87-94
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1973 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0891)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1973 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0892)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1973 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0893)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1973 January 10; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0894)
  - Clemson, 1973 January 13
    Duke win; score: 75-73
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1973 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0895)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1973 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0896)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1973 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0897)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1973 January 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0898)
  - Davidson, 1973 January 17
    Duke win; score: 78-75
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1973 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0899)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1973 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0900)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1973 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0901)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 4, 1973 January 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0902)
  - North Carolina, 1973 January 19
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1973 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0903)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1973 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0904)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1973 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0905)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1973 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0906)
  - North Carolina, 1973 January 20
    Duke loss; score: 71-82
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1973 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0907)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1973 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0908)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1973 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0909)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1973 January 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0910)
  - Maryland, 1973 February 03
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1973 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0911)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1973 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0912)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1973 February 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0913)
  - Wake Forest, 1973 February 07
    Duke win; score: 84-71
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1973 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0914)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1973 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0915)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1973 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0916)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1973 February 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0917)
  - Virginia, 1973 February 13
    Duke win; score: 90-66
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1973 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0918)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1973 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0919)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1973 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 20, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0920)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1973 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0921)
  - Notre Dame, 1973 February 17
    Duke win; score: 86-74
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 1, 1973 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0922)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 2, 1973 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0923)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 3, 1973 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0924)
    - Duke vs. Notre Dame: Reel 4, 1973 February 17; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0925)
  - NC State, 1973 February 21
    Duke loss; score: 50-74
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1973 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0926)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1973 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0927)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1973 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0928)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1973 February 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 19, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0929)
  - North Carolina, 1973 March 03
    Duke loss; score: 70-72
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1973 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0930)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1973 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0931)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1973 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0932)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1973 March 03; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0933)
  - Virginia, 1973 March 08
    Duke loss; score: 55-59; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1973 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0934)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1973 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0935)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1973 March 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0936)
  - North Carolina, 1973 March 13
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1973 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0939)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1973 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0940)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1973 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0941)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel Cutaways, 1973 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0937)
      Reel is labled "Duke vs. NC State cutaways" and dated 1973 March 13; it is most likely Duke vs. UNC.
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel Slo mo, 1973 March 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 21, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0938)
  - East Carolina, 1973 December 01
    Duke win; score: 82-69
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1973 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0942)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1973 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0943)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 3, 1973 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0944)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 4, 1973 December 01; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0945)
  - Virginia, 1973 December 08
    Duke loss; score: 82-104
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1973 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0946)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1973 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0947)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1973 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0948)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1973 December 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 22, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0949)
  - Western Kentucky, 1973 December 26
    Duke win; score: 75-69; Gator Bowl Classic, Jacksonville, Florida
    - Duke vs. Western Kentucky: Reel 1, 1973 December 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0950)
    - Duke vs. Western Kentucky: Reel 2, 1973 December 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0951)
    - Duke vs. Western Kentucky: Reel 3, 1973 December 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0952)
    - Duke vs. Western Kentucky: Reel 4, 1973 December 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0953)
  - Florida, 1973 December 27
    Duke loss; score: 60-77; Gator Bowl Classic, Jacksonville, Florida
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 1, 1973 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0954)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 2, 1973 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0955)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 3, 1973 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0956)
    - Duke vs. Florida: Reel 4, 1973 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0957)
  - Wake Forest, 1974 January 04
    Duke loss; score: 61-64; Big Four Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1974 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0962)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1974 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0963)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1974 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0964)
  - North Carolina, 1974 January 05
    Duke loss; score: 75-84; Big Four Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1974 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0965)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1974 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0966)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1974 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0967)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1974 January 05; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0968)
  - Clemson, 1974 January 16
    Duke win; score: 63-50
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 1, 1974 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0969)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 2, 1974 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0970)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 3, 1974 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0971)
    - Duke vs. Clemson: Reel 4, 1974 January 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0972)
  - North Carolina, 1974 January 19
    Duke loss; score: 71-73
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0973)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0974)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0975)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0976)
  - North Carolina, 1974 January 19
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0977)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0978)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0979)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1974 January 19; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0980)
  - Wake Forest, 1974 January 23
    Duke loss; score: 71-90
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1974 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0981)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1974 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0982)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1974 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0983)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1974 January 23; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0984)
  - Princeton, 1974 January 26
    Duke win; score: 73-65
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 1, 1974 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0985)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 2, 1974 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0986)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 3, 1974 January 26; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 24, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0987)
  - Davidson, 1974 January 30
    Duke win; score: 89-72
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 1, 1974 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0988)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 2, 1974 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0989)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 3, 1974 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0990)
    - Duke vs. Davidson: Reel 4, 1974 January 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 23, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0991)
  - Maryland, 1974 February 02
    Duke loss; score: 83-104
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1974 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0992)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1974 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0993)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1974 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0994)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1974 February 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0995)
  - NC State, 1974 February 04
    Duke loss; score: 78-92
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1974 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0996)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1974 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0997)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1974 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0998)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1974 February 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0999)
  - Wake Forest, 1974 February 06
    Duke loss; score: 67-74
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1974 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1000)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1974 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1001)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1974 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1002)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1974 February 06; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1003)
  - Virginia, 1974 February 13
    Duke win; score: 88-78
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1974 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1004)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1974 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1005)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1974 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1006)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1974 February 13; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1007)
  - Virginia, 1974 February 14
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 1, 1974 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1008)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 2, 1974 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1009)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 3, 1974 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1010)
    - Duke vs. Virginia: Reel 4, 1974 February 14; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1011)
  - NC State, 1974 February 20
    Duke loss; score: 87-113
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 1, 1974 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1012)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 2, 1974 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1013)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 3, 1974 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 25, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1014)
    - Duke vs. NC State: Reel 4, 1974 February 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1015)
  - Maryland, 1974 February 25
    Duke loss; score: 61-64
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1974 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1016)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1974 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1017)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1974 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1018)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1974 February 25; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1019)
  - North Carolina, 1974 March 02
    Duke loss; score: 92-96
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, 1974 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1020)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, 1974 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1021)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 3, 1974 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1022)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 4, 1974 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1023)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 5, 1974 March 02; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1024)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Unidentified game film coverage, 1974 March 02; BetaCamSP
  - Maryland, 1974 March 07
    Duke loss; score: 66-85; ACC Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1974 March 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1025)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1974 March 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1026)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1974 March 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 26, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1027)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1974 March 07; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1028)
  - St. Kilda, 1974 November 16
    Duke win; score: 119-66
    - Duke vs. St. Kilda: Reel 1, 1974 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1029)
    - Duke vs. St. Kilda: Reel 2, 1974 November 16; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1030)
  - Cornell, 1974 November 30
    Duke win; score: 100-62
    - Duke vs. Cornell: Reel 1, 1974 November 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1031)
    - Duke vs. Cornell: Reel 2, 1974 November 30; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1032)
  - East Carolina, 1974 December 04
    Duke win; score: 79-73
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 1, 1974 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1033)
    - Duke vs. East Carolina: Reel 2, 1974 December 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1034)
  - Louisiana State, 1974 December 20
    Duke loss; score: 95-105; Carolina Classic, Columbia, SC
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 1, 1974 December 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1035)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 2, 1974 December 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1036)
    - Duke vs. Louisiana State: Reel 3, 1974 December 20; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 200, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1037)
      This reel also contains Duke-Pittsburgh (12/27/1974) and Duke-Kent State (12/28/1974)
  - Princeton, 1974 December 21
    Duke win; score: 66-57; Carolina Classic, Columbia, SC
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 1, 1974 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1038)
    - Duke vs. Princeton: Reel 2, 1974 December 21; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1039)
  - Pittsburgh, 1974 December 27
    Duke win; score: 89-75; Holiday Doubleheader, Reynolds, Raleigh, NC
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Bill Foster sideline views, 1974 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1040)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh: Reel 2, 1974 December 27; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 200, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1037)
      This reel also contains Duke-Louisiana State (12/20/1974) and Duke-Kent State (12/28/1974)
  - Kent State, 1974 December 28
    Duke win; score: 83-65; Holiday Doubleheader, Raleigh, NC
    - Duke vs. Kent State: Reel 1, 1974 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1042)
    - Duke vs. Kent State: Reel 2, 1974 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1043)
    - Duke vs. Kent State: Reel 3, 1974 December 28; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 200, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1037)
      This reel also contains Duke-Louisiana State (12/20/1974) and Duke-Pittsburgh (12/27/1974)
  - North Carolina, 1975 January 03
    Duke win; score 99-96; at Greensboro Colisseum
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 1, circa 1974-1975; 16mm film: 3" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0958)
    - Duke vs. North Carolina: Reel 2, circa 1974-1975; 16mm film: 3" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0959)
  - Wake Forest, 1975 January 04
    Duke loss; score: 71-75; Big Four Tournament, Greensboro, NC
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 1, 1975 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1045)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 2, 1975 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1046)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 3, 1975 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1047)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Reel 4, 1975 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 27, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1048)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest: Duke offense only, 1975 January 04; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 200, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1049)
  - Maryland, 1975 January 08
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 1, 1975 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1050)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 2, 1975 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1051)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 3, 1975 January 08; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1052)
    - Duke vs. Maryland: Reel 4, 1975 January 08; 16mm film: 3" reel (Box 198, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-0960)
  - South Florida, 1975 January 11
    Duke win; score: 95-86
    - Duke vs. South Florida: Reel 1, 1975 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1053)
    - Duke vs. South Florida: Reel 2, 1975 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 28, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1054)
    - Duke vs. South Florida: Reel 3, 1975 January 11; 16mm film: 7" reel (Box 200, Film-reel UA13010005-F16-1055)